[Music]
this is your DVD to come back home and
walk but your display is in your day for
the Hat song time is going to fail now
watch as I reanimate the show that you
are banned in dismantled miss hammer but
we won't be skipped Oh sway trapped
within this show you let the source to
drift away will the show's decay the
song that baby but here if I come today
you see you made mad dog that because
you can't for hit TV show it's been
canceled for we move forward it's not
going to come back today s user live in
more alive you will to create a queue
trailer hey came as one people 5 you
exactly what we need to build up our TV
show working at 9 you feel good
[Music]
so you found all that so you start a
meal huh a song well great offices are
great but the ending is just the same
now I'm not your head to the beat of the
music as you reach the for now the
sensation of the capsulation than anger
to your song you see we have know how
our soul that will cut you just for your
portray or to tell some type of music
and fawns but sure this inevitably ends
the farm splash of eternal hate will
flow the flow and clean your flag now
will tools near for so I'm gonna come
back today as he's alive in more alive
[Music]
you